

CONTACT

25 Crosbie Yard, Ossory Road North Strand, Dublin, Ireland. cardosodecarvalhot@gmail.com 353 83 002 7576

SKILLS

Leadership experience
Difficult decisions taker
Management knowledge
Financial and sales experience
Advanced proficiency in excel
Team worker
Quick learner
Customer orientation
Committed and pro-active

EDUCATION

Administration | 2005 - 2010 Universidade Federal de Pernambuco - Recife - Brazil

LANGUAGES

Advanced English
Native Portuguese

Thiago Cardoso de Carvalho

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am an administrator with more than 10 years of experience in different markets: customer support, sales, public sector, farming, financial management and logistics. I have held leadership positions and I am experienced in critical analysis for difficult decisions.

WORK HISTORY

Voice Peaker

09/2022 - current

Musgrave - Dublin - Ireland

Reponsible for picking products according to client's orders, with a high level of organization. Equally responsible for assisting other tasks in the warehouse.

Farmer 05/2020 – 06/2022

Self-employed - Pedras de Fogo - Brazil

Papaya producer. Responsible for all the agricultural activities: planting, fertilizing, spraying, harvesting, production trading and general management.

Administrative Manager

05/2018 - 12/2020

Pedras de Fogo City Hall - Pedras de Fogo - Brazil

Responsible for the administratition of two departments, managing the planning and control of budgets, cashflows, contracts, payments, purchasing, debts equalization, accounting and bank account transactions. Also responsible for indicators controlling, achievement of government goals and strategic decisions.

Administrative Manager

10/2016 - 04/2018

Mutum and Neem Brazil - Dois Irmãos do Tocantins - Brazil

Responsible for the management of two soybean farms, embracing structural organization, production flow, production trade, budgets, cashflows, payments, purchasing, accountability, banking operations, issuing invoices, contracts supervision, debts equalization, strategic decisions and general administration.

Sales Supervisor

04/2014 - 09/2016

Olenka Cosméticos - São Paulo - Brazil

Responsible for supervision, sellings, selection, training and customer support of authorized dealers in six brazilian states, as well as responsible for resolving and negotiating payment-related issues.

Vendor

01/2011 - 03/2014

Cardomassa - Itambé - Brazil

Responsible for sales and after-sales activities, such as conquest of new clients, negotiation of debits, promotional actions and customer support.